[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tacloban"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "And what are you hearing about the scale of devastation down there and indeed, the other islands you touched on which they may not even have got to, yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Yeah, we are actually -- we're flying in to Tacloban about two hours ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "Do they have any idea yet on the 6th times that this hit the islands, how many of those islands have been affected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "At this point no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "What is the best way to help right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "It has to be through the international aid agencies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "What was your thought as you were taking it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Hi, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "What is the impression that you're getting on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Absolutely correct, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "I mean in terms of the terminology used here, is there much substantial difference between a massive storm surge like this and a tsunami?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Really, just small technicalities.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "When did you realize this was a really massive storm?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well we were already getting ready for the massive storm because we knew it was a very strong super typhoon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "TO", "IN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "And what was the feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Oh, the wind was -- I can describe this to on like -- it was very scary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What do you think is the most desperate need right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, actually, the desperate need of course is food, water, shelter right now because all the homes are destroyed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Is it really getting worse or is this a predictable weather pattern that recurs from generation to generation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, first of all, this wasn't the biggest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, my view is that of a journalist to introduce a lot of scientist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Isn't under compensating, under reacting denying climate change in the end more dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Well, even though I'm a skeptic, I don't know of anyone that denies climate change.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", ":", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "PENCER: Which part is not true, Mark?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "You should not do that, sir -- to say that we don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Administration"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "So John the rumor is as going to the Wall Street Journal that just 50,000 people in America had so far enrolled into ObamaCare, if that is true, that is pretty appalling isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "It's a dismal number Piers, the Administration, you know, won't confirm this numbers but they're not disputing them and they are supposed to put out their own numbers later this week and it sounds like they're just going to take that better pill once this week officially on the record if you will when they do that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "If these figures carry on that level, would you be buying any stock in Kathleen Sebelius?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Look, there's no question the President is going to stay with her through this storm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathleen Sebelius"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "From what you went through, what is the hardest thing to deal with and how do you deal with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Gosh, there are so many different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "What's my game plan to survive this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Incredibly, you've carried on being a great mom, working ridiculously hard as I'm sure Amy will too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "You know, continuing, trying to live a normal life, how easy is that to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I think that, you know, I called cancer a bit of a blessing, because it puts your life in perspective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What's the reality like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "You know, I would imagine it's different for different women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "NNPS", "VBD", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Final question, how are you feeling?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "I feel great, my prognosis is excellent and I chanted a bit when they said, \"Will you come and join Piers tonight?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "How important is early to detection and immediate action?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "You know, prevention does not yet exist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "But do you think it's essential in cases like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Angelina Jolie"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "It's obviously not a club Zoraida that anybody wants to be a member of, but how important is it for public figures do you think to be as courageous as you have been and others in that position like Angelina?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, it was Angelina Jolie who gave me the courage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 439, "question": "How is she doing and how is she coping having announced to all this to the world with the reality of what her life now is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "You know, I think she said it best in her op-ed, \"She feels no less of a women.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "So, what time do you getting up tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "1:30, really soon here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Can you give us any indication at the moment of the scale of this disaster?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "And obviously there are a number of typhoons every season in the Philippines, is this the worst that you can ever remember?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Philippines"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "And are you getting the international help that you need and is it coming fast enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "Oh yes, we have 22 countries that have already pledged financial assistance, medical assistance, rescue and relief volunteers, temporary shelters like tents and so on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}, "docId": "131111pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What is the best way that they can get that information?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Well, we're urging them to contact the Google website that has been set up for missing persons, the embassy and the consulate also is providing numbers that they can contact in case they want to get information from us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]